Rahmad Fahrurrozi

Glenmore, Banyuwangi, jawa Timur | (+62)857-4657-4319 | zfahrur150105@gmail.com

<u>LinkedIn</u> | Web portofolio | GitHub

About Me

2st semester student of Banyuwangi State Polytechnic majoring in Business and Informatics. Expertise includes web programming with mastery of several programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Python. In addition, I'm also has the ability to use the Tailwind css framework, React js framework and can operate figma as a support for web design and development.

Skills

- HTML (Intermediate)
- CSS (Intermwdiate)
- JavaScript (Intermediate)
- PHP (Beginner)

- Python (Intermadiate)
- Tailwind (Beginner)
- Figma (Beginner)
- React JS (Beginner)
- Wordpress (Intermediate)

Experience

 (CO) information technology division and da'wah communication in ROHIS organization, deputy secretary of commission B on MPK organization (assembly class representative)

 videographer + editing in the competition village profile creation 2022-2023

2020-2021

Education

SMAN 1 Glenmore

2020-2023

- mathematics and science
- Banyuwangi State Polytechnic

2020-Now

Business & Informatics